
module.exports = [
  { question: 'ما هي مواعيد الشحن؟', answer: 'الشحن بيتم خلال 1 إلى 3 أيام عمل داخل القاهرة والجيزة.' },
  { question: 'ما هي مواعيد العمل؟', answer: 'إحنا متاحين كل يوم من 10 صباحًا حتى 8 مساءً، ماعدا يوم الجمعة.' },
  { question: 'هل يمكنني استرجاع المنتج؟', answer: 'نعم، يمكنك استرجاع المنتج في غضون 14 يومًا من تاريخ الاستلام بشرط أن يكون في حالته الأصلية.' },
  { question: 'ما هي طرق الدفع المتاحة؟', answer: 'نقبل الدفع عبر البطاقة الائتمانية، PayPal، والدفع عند الاستلام.' },
  { question: 'هل يمكنني تعديل طلبي؟', answer: 'يمكنك تعديل طلبك قبل أن يتم شحنه، تواصل معنا عبر الدعم الفني.' },
  
,
      {
        "question": "من أنتم؟",
        "answer": "نحن طلاب من كلية العلوم جامعة القاهرة قسم الحاسب، ونعمل على مشروع للمادة 303 مع الدكتور الجيار وسامح."
      },
      {
        "question": "من أين أنتم؟",
        "answer": "نحن من مصر."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هو اسم التيم الذي طور التطبيق؟",
        "answer": "تيم SuperMall."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هو تطبيق SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "تطبيق SuperMall هو تطبيق هتلاقي عليه كل ما تحتاج من منتجات وتقدر تقول عليه أحسن من أمازون."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هي المنتجات التي يقدمها SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نحن نقدم منتجات متنوعة مثل الملابس والمنتجات التقنية."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما الذي يميز SuperMall عن غيره من المواقع؟",
        "answer": "نحن أفضل وأسرع من باقي المواقع بفرق شاسع من ناحية الشحن والجودة لدى تجارنا."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هي مواعيد العمل في SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نحن نعمل كل أيام الأسبوع من الساعة 8 صباحًا إلى الساعة 12 مساءً."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يوجد شحن مجاني؟",
        "answer": "نعم، وأوقات ممكن يكون شحن مجاني."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل تشحنون لكل المحافظات؟",
        "answer": "نعم، الشحن يتم لجميع المحافظات."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يوجد دفع عند الاستلام؟",
        "answer": "نعم، يوجد إمكانية للدفع عند الاستلام."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هي مدة الشحن؟",
        "answer": "أوقات الشحن تصل إلى 14 يوم كحد أقصى."
      },
      {
        "question": "على أي نظام يعمل التطبيق؟",
        "answer": "نظام التطبيق يعمل على React Native."
      },
      {
        "question": "كيف يمكن التواصل مع فريق الدعم؟",
        "answer": "يمكن التواصل مع فريق الدعم من خلال الشات بوت أو عبر صفحتنا على فيسبوك."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل هناك عروض؟",
        "answer": "نعم، معظم السنة توجد عروض وتخفيضات، ويمكن للعملاء تصفح المنتجات لمتابعة العروض."
      }
  
 ,
      {
        "question": "ما هو SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "SuperMall هو تطبيق تجارة إلكترونية حديث يقدم لك تجربة تسوق سلسة وسريعة. سواء كنت تبحث عن أحدث المنتجات أو العروض الحصرية أو أفضل الأسعار، نحن هنا لتلبية احتياجاتك."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هي مهمة SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "هدفنا هو تقديم أفضل تجربة تسوق عبر الإنترنت مع خدمة عالية الجودة، مما يجعل التسوق أكثر متعة وسهولة للجميع."
      },
      {
        "question": "من هم أعضاء فريق SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "فريق SuperMall يتكون من مجموعة من الطلاب المبدعين من كلية العلوم جامعة القاهرة. أعضاء الفريق هم: أحمد عز الدين خليلي، عبد الرحمن أحمد حلمي، بافلي ممتاز، رمضان عبد الناصر، أحمد سعيد، أنس جمال، عبد الرحمن إيهاب، عبد الله علي خميس."
      },
      {
        "question": "ماذا يقدم SuperMall للمستخدمين؟",
        "answer": "SuperMall يقدم لك كل ما تحتاجه من منتجات في مختلف الفئات مثل الملابس والمنتجات التقنية، وكل ذلك مع تجربة تسوق سريعة وسهلة."
      },
      {
        "question": "كيف يمكنني الوصول إلى فريق دعم SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "يمكنك التواصل مع فريق الدعم عبر الشات بوت أو من خلال صفحتنا على فيسبوك."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يوجد شحن مجاني؟",
        "answer": "نعم، لدينا أوقات عرض شحن مجاني للعملاء."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هي مواعيد العمل في SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نحن نعمل يوميًا من الساعة 8 صباحًا وحتى الساعة 12 مساءً."
      },
      {
        "question": "من أين يأتي فريق SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "فريق SuperMall هو مجموعة من الطلاب من مصر، ومن كلية العلوم جامعة القاهرة قسم الحاسب."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما الذي يميز SuperMall عن باقي المواقع؟",
        "answer": "نحن أفضل وأسرع من باقي المواقع بفرق شاسع من ناحية الشحن والجودة، وكل ذلك بفضل تجارنا الموثوقين."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يمكنني الدفع عند الاستلام؟",
        "answer": "نعم، نحن نقدم خيار الدفع عند الاستلام لجميع العملاء."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هو الحد الأقصى لمدة الشحن؟",
        "answer": "أوقات الشحن لدينا تصل إلى 14 يوم كحد أقصى."
      },
      {
        "question": "على أي منصة يعمل تطبيق SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "تطبيق SuperMall يعمل على React Native، مما يوفر لك تجربة مستخدم رائعة وسلسة على جميع الأجهزة."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يمكنني متابعة العروض على SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نعم، لدينا عروض مستمرة طوال العام، ويمكنك متابعة أحدث العروض والتخفيضات عبر تصفح المنتجات على التطبيق."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يوجد شحن إلى كل المحافظات؟",
        "answer": "نعم، نحن نوفر خدمة الشحن لجميع المحافظات في مصر."
      },
      {
        "question": "من قام بتطوير الشات بوت؟",
        "answer": "الشات بوت تم تطويره بواسطة  حلمي."
      },
      {
        "question": "ما هو SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "SuperMall هو منصة تسوق إلكترونية تتيح لك شراء كل ما تحتاجه من ملابس، منتجات تقنية، وغيرها من المنتجات، بكل سهولة وسرعة."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يمكنني شراء الملابس من SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بالملابس لجميع الأذواق والمقاسات."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يمكنني شراء أجهزة إلكترونية من SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "بالطبع، لدينا مجموعة متنوعة من المنتجات التقنية من الهواتف الذكية والأجهزة الإلكترونية الأخرى."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يقدم SuperMall عروض خصم؟",
        "answer": "نعم، نحن نقدم خصومات وعروض مستمرة طوال العام على مختلف المنتجات."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يمكنني تصفح المنتجات على SuperMall بسهولة؟",
        "answer": "نعم، يمكنك تصفح جميع المنتجات بسهولة عبر التطبيق أو الموقع الإلكتروني."
      },
      {
        "question": "هل يتوفر شحن مجاني في SuperMall؟",
        "answer": "نعم، في أوقات معينة، نقدم شحن مجاني لجميع عملائنا."
      }
 ,
 {
  "question": "ما هي مواعيد العمل في SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "نحن نعمل كل أيام الأسبوع من الساعة 8 صباحًا إلى الساعة 12 مساءً."
}
,
{
  "question": "هل يوجد شحن مجاني؟",
  "answer": "نعم، وأوقات ممكن يكون شحن مجاني."
},
{
  "question": "هل تشحنون لكل المحافظات؟",
  "answer": "نعم، الشحن يتم لجميع المحافظات."
},
{
  "question": "هل يوجد دفع عند الاستلام؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يوجد إمكانية للدفع عند الاستلام."
},
{
  "question": "ما هي مدة الشحن؟",
  "answer": "أوقات الشحن تصل إلى 14 يوم كحد أقصى."
},
{
  "question": "على أي نظام يعمل التطبيق؟",
  "answer": "نظام التطبيق يعمل على React Native."
},
{
  "question": "كيف يمكن التواصل مع فريق الدعم؟",
  "answer": "يمكن التواصل مع فريق الدعم من خلال الشات بوت أو عبر صفحتنا على فيسبوك."
},
{
  "question": "هل هناك عروض؟",
  "answer": "نعم، معظم السنة توجد عروض وتخفيضات، ويمكن للعملاء تصفح المنتجات لمتابعة العروض."
},

{
  "question": "هل يمكنني شراء الطعام من SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "حالياً لا نقدم خدمات شراء الطعام، ولكن هناك خطط لإضافة منتجات غذائية في المستقبل."
},
{
  "question": "هل يتوفر دعم متعدد اللغات في التطبيق؟",
  "answer": "حاليًا التطبيق يدعم اللغة العربية فقط."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني تتبع حالة طلبي؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يمكنك تتبع حالة طلبك عبر التطبيق أو من خلال رابط الشحن المرسل لك."
},
{
  "question": "هل يقدم SuperMall خصومات خاصة للعملاء الجدد؟",
  "answer": "نعم، نقدم خصومات خاصة للعملاء الجدد عند التسجيل في التطبيق لأول مرة."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني شراء هدايا من SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يمكنك شراء هدايا من مختلف الأقسام مثل الملابس والإلكترونيات."
},
{
  "question": "هل يتم تحديث الأسعار في SuperMall بانتظام؟",
  "answer": "نعم، الأسعار يتم تحديثها بشكل دوري لتتناسب مع السوق."
},
{
  "question": "ما هي شروط الاسترجاع في SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "يجب أن يكون المنتج في حالته الأصلية مع وجود الفاتورة خلال 14 يومًا من استلامه."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني إلغاء طلبي بعد الدفع؟",
  "answer": "يمكنك إلغاء الطلب قبل شحنه، وتواصل مع فريق الدعم لإتمام الإلغاء."
},
{
  "question": "هل يوجد خدمة عملاء 24/7؟",
  "answer": "نحن متاحون من الساعة 8 صباحًا حتى الساعة 12 مساءً يوميًا باستثناء الجمعة."
},
{
  "question": "هل يوجد خدمة تغليف الهدايا؟",
  "answer": "حالياً، لا نقدم خدمة تغليف الهدايا."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني شراء أجهزة منزلية من SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بالأجهزة المنزلية مثل الغسالات، الميكروويف، وغيرها."
},
{
  "question": "هل يتم إضافة منتجات جديدة بشكل دوري؟",
  "answer": "نعم، نحن نقوم بإضافة منتجات جديدة بشكل دوري في مختلف الفئات."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني شراء منتجات من علامات تجارية مشهورة؟",
  "answer": "نعم، لدينا منتجات من علامات تجارية مشهورة في فئات مختلفة."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني التواصل مع دعم العملاء عبر الهاتف؟",
  "answer": "حاليًا، الدعم متاح فقط عبر الشات بوت أو صفحتنا على فيسبوك."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنك أن ترسل لي رابط للمنتج؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يمكننا إرسال رابط للمنتج عبر التطبيق أو عبر البريد الإلكتروني."
},

{
  "question": "ما هي أنواع الدفع المتاحة في SuperMall؟",
  "answer": "نحن نقبل الدفع عبر البطاقة الائتمانية، PayPal، والدفع عند الاستلام."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني تغيير عنوان الشحن بعد تقديم الطلب؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يمكن تغيير العنوان بشرط أن يكون الطلب لم يتم شحنه بعد."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني شراء منتجات جديدة عبر الموقع؟",
  "answer": "نعم، يمكنك شراء منتجات جديدة بسهولة عبر الموقع أو التطبيق."
},
{
  "question": "هل لديكم أقسام خاصة بالمنتجات الرجالية؟",
  "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بالمنتجات الرجالية من ملابس وأكسسوارات."
},
{
  "question": "هل يمكنني الحصول على شهادة ضمان للمنتجات؟",
  "answer": "نعم، نقدم شهادة ضمان لبعض المنتجات، وفقًا لسياسة المصنع."
}
  
  ,    {
    "question": "هل يوجد خصم للطلبات الكبيرة؟",
    "answer": "نعم، نقدم خصومات تصل إلى 20% للطلبات التي تزيد عن 1000 جنيه."
},
{
    "question": "كيف يمكنني إنشاء حساب في SuperMall؟",
    "answer": "يمكنك إنشاء حساب بسهولة عن طريق البريد الإلكتروني أو رقم الهاتف عبر التطبيق أو الموقع."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني حفظ المنتجات في قائمة المفضلة؟",
    "answer": "نعم، يمكنك إضافة أي منتج إلى المفضلة بالنقر على أيقونة القلب بجوار المنتج."
},
{
    "question": "ما هي سياسة الخصوصية في SuperMall؟",
    "answer": "نحن نحترم خصوصية عملائنا ولا نشارك بياناتك الشخصية مع أي جهات خارجية."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني شراء منتجات للحيوانات الأليفة؟",
    "answer": "حاليًا لا نقدم منتجات للحيوانات الأليفة ولكنها قد تضاف في المستقبل."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد قسم للكتب في SuperMall؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم للكتب بمختلف أنواعها بما في ذلك الكتب التعليمية والروايات."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني شراء منتجات رياضية؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بالمنتجات الرياضية والأدوات الرياضية."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد تطبيق خاص بـ SuperMall للأندرويد؟",
    "answer": "نعم، يمكنك تحميل تطبيقنا الرسمي من متجر جوجل بلاي."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد تطبيق SuperMall للآيفون؟",
    "answer": "نعم، التطبيق متاح على متجر آبل للتحميل."
},
{
    "question": "كيف يمكنني إعادة تعيين كلمة المرور؟",
    "answer": "يمكنك استخدام خاصية 'نسيت كلمة المرور' في صفحة تسجيل الدخول."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني تغيير لغة التطبيق؟",
    "answer": "حاليًا التطبيق يدعم اللغة العربية فقط."
},
{
    "question": "ما هي شروط استخدام SuperMall؟",
    "answer": "يمكنك الاطلاع على شروط الاستخدام الكاملة في قسم 'الشروط والأحكام' بالموقع."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني مشاركة المنتجات مع الأصدقاء؟",
    "answer": "نعم، يوجد زر مشاركة بجانب كل منتج لمشاركته عبر وسائل التواصل."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد نظام تقييم للمنتجات؟",
    "answer": "نعم، يمكنك تقييم المنتجات التي قمت بشرائها من خلال حسابك."
},
{
    "question": "كيف يمكنني معرفة المقاسات المتوفرة للملابس؟",
    "answer": "جميع المقاسات المتوفرة تظهر في صفحة المنتج تحت قسم 'المقاسات'."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني طلب منتج غير متوفر حالياً؟",
    "answer": "نعم، يمكنك التواصل مع خدمة العملاء لطلب منتج غير متوفر."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد قسم للأطفال في SuperMall?",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بملابس وألعاب الأطفال."
},
{
    "question": "هل يمكنني شراء منتجات التجميل؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم خاص بمستحضرات التجميل والعناية الشخصية."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد قسم للعطور؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا مجموعة متنوعة من العطور المحلية والعالمية."
},

{
    "question": "متى تبدأ العروض التخفيضية في SuperMall?",
    "answer": "العروض التخفيضية تبدأ عادة في المناسبات والأعياد ونعلن عنها مسبقًا."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد عرض خاص في الأعياد؟",
    "answer": "نعم، نقدم عروضًا خاصة في جميع الأعياد والمناسبات."
},
{
    "question": "كيف أعرف أن المنتج عليه تخفيض؟",
    "answer": "المنتجات المخفضة عليها علامة التخفيض ويظهر السعر قبل وبعد التخفيض."
},

{
    "question": "كيف أتأكد من جودة المنتجات؟",
    "answer": "جميع المنتجات لدينا من موردين موثوقين ويمكنك قراءة تقييمات العملاء."
},
{
    "question": "هل تقدمون ضمانًا على الأجهزة الإلكترونية؟",
    "answer": "نعم، الأجهزة الإلكترونية تأتي بضمان المصنع الرسمي."
},

{
    "question": "كيف أصبح شريكًا في SuperMall؟",
    "answer": "يمكنك التواصل مع قسم الشراكات عبر الموقع الرسمي."
},
{
    "question": "هل لديكم برنامج تسويق بالعمولة؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا برنامج تسويق بالعمولة يمكنك الانضمام إليه."
},

{
    "question": "ما هي متطلبات تشغيل التطبيق؟",
    "answer": "التطبيق يعمل على أندرويد 8 أو أعلى، وآيفون iOS 12 أو أحدث."
},
{
    "question": "هل التطبيق آمن للاستخدام؟",
    "answer": "نعم، التطبيق آمن تمامًا ويستخدم تشفيرًا لحماية بياناتك."
},

{
    "question": "هل يمكنني اختيار موعد الاستلام؟",
    "answer": "نعم، في بعض المناطق يمكنك تحديد موعد الاستلام المناسب لك."
},
{
    "question": "ما هي شركات الشحن التي تتعاملون معها؟",
    "answer": "نتعامل مع عدة شركات شحن موثوقة لضمان وصول طلبك بأمان."
},


{
    "question": "هل تبيعون أثاث منزلي؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم للأثاث المنزلي بمختلف أنواعه."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد أواني طبخ في SuperMall?",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا مجموعة متنوعة من أواني الطبخ والمطبخ."
},


{
    "question": "هل تبيعون أجهزة تكييف؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا تشكيلة من أجهزة التكييف بماركات عالمية."
},
{
    "question": "هل يوجد غسالات أطباق؟",
    "answer": "نعم، لدينا قسم كامل للأجهزة المنزلية بما فيها غسالات الأطباق."
},


  {
      "question": "ما هي أحدث هواتف آيفون المتوفرة لديكم؟",
      "answer": "لدينا أحدث موديلات آيفون بما فيها iPhone 15 Pro Max بسعر 45,000 جنيه، iPhone 15 Pro بسعر 40,000 جنيه، و iPhone 15 بسعر 35,000 جنيه. جميعها بشاشات Super Retina XDR ومعالجات A16 Bionic."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد هواتف سامسونج جالاكسي S23؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا سامسونج جالاكسي S23 Ultra بسعر 38,000 جنيه بشاشة ديناميك AMOLED 2X مقاس 6.8 بوصة، وكاميرا 200 ميجابكسل، وجالاكسي S23+ بسعر 32,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أرخص هاتف ذكي لديكم؟",
      "answer": "هاتف Realme C35 بسعر 5,999 جنيه بشاشة 6.6 بوصة، كاميرا ثلاثية 50 ميجابكسل، وبطارية 5000 مللي أمبير."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل تبيعون هواتف شاومي؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا شاومي ريدمي نوت 12 برو بسعر 12,999 جنيه، وشاومي 13T برو بسعر 24,999 جنيه بمواصفات عالية الجودة."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أفضل هاتف للألعاب لديكم؟",
      "answer": "هاتف ASUS ROG Phone 7 بسعر 30,000 جنيه بمعالج Snapdragon 8 Gen 2، شاشة AMOLED 165Hz، وتبريد فعال للألعاب الثقيلة."
  },

  {
      "question": "ما هي أجهزة اللابتوب المتوفرة لديكم؟",
      "answer": "لدينا تشكيلة متنوعة من اللابتوبات تشمل: Dell Inspiron 15 بسعر 18,000 جنيه، HP Pavilion بسعر 22,000 جنيه، Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 بسعر 25,000 جنيه، وMacBook Air M2 بسعر 35,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد لابتوبات للألعاب؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا لابتوبات مخصصة للألعاب مثل: MSI Katana GF76 بسعر 40,000 جنيه، ASUS TUF Gaming F15 بسعر 38,000 جنيه، وAcer Nitro 5 بسعر 35,000 جنيه بمواصفات عالية للألعاب."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أرخص لابتوب لديكم؟",
      "answer": "لابتوب Lenovo IdeaPad 1 بسعر 12,000 جنيه بشاشة 14 بوصة، معالج Intel Celeron، و4GB رام، مناسب للمهام الأساسية."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد أجهزة ماك بوك؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا MacBook Air M1 بسعر 30,000 جنيه، MacBook Air M2 بسعر 35,000 جنيه، وMacBook Pro 14 بوصة M2 Pro بسعر 65,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أفضل لابتوب للبرمجة؟",
      "answer": "نوصي بـ Dell XPS 15 بسعر 55,000 جنيه بمعالج Core i7، 16GB رام، و512GB SSD، أو MacBook Pro 14 بوصة للمطورين الذين يعملون على أنظمة Apple."
  },

  {
      "question": "ما هي التابلتات المتوفرة لديكم؟",
      "answer": "لدينا: iPad 10th Gen بسعر 18,000 جنيه، Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 بسعر 25,000 جنيه، Huawei MatePad بسعر 12,000 جنيه، وLenovo Tab P11 بسعر 9,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد ايباد برو؟",
      "answer": "نعم، iPad Pro 11 بوصة M2 بسعر 32,000 جنيه، وiPad Pro 12.9 بوصة M2 بسعر 45,000 جنيه بشاشة Liquid Retina XDR."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أفضل تابلت للرسم الرقمي؟",
      "answer": "iPad Pro مع قلم Apple Pencil هو الخيار الأمثل للرسم الرقمي، أو Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 مع قلم S-Pen الذي يأتي مع الشاشة AMOLED."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد تابلتات للأطفال؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا تابلت Lenovo Tab M10 Kids Edition بسعر 6,000 جنيه مع حماية مضادة للصدمات ومحتوى تعليمي مدمج."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أرخص تابلت لديكم؟",
      "answer": "تابلت Samsung Galaxy Tab A7 Lite بسعر 4,500 جنيه بشاشة 8.7 بوصة، مناسب للمهام الأساسية ومشاهدة الفيديوهات."
  },

  {
      "question": "ما هي أنواع التكييفات المتوفرة لديكم؟",
      "answer": "لدينا تكييفات شارب، تورنيدو، كاريير، وجري بجميع أنواعها (سبليت، شباك، ستاند) وبقدرات مختلفة تبدأ من 1.5 حصان حتى 3 حصان."
  },
  {
      "question": "كم سعر تكييف شارب 1.5 حصان؟",
      "answer": "تكييف شارب سبليت 1.5 حصان بارد ساخن بسعر 18,000 جنيه مع ضمان 5 سنوات على الضاغط."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد تكييفات إنفرتر؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا تكييف جري إنفرتر 1.5 حصان A++ بسعر 22,000 جنيه يوفر حتى 60% من استهلاك الكهرباء."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أفضل تكييف من حيث توفير الكهرباء؟",
      "answer": "تكييف تورنيدو إنفرتر 1.5 حصان فئة A+++ هو الأفضل في التوفير بسعر 24,000 جنيه مع تقنية التحكم الذكي في الطاقة."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل تقدمون خدمة تركيب التكييفات؟",
      "answer": "نعم، نقدم خدمة التركيب المجاني مع أي تكييف تشتريه من خلالنا مع ضمان التركيب لمدة عام."
  },

  {
      "question": "هل يوجد غسالات أتوماتيك؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا غسالات توشيبا، سامسونج، وإل جي بسعات مختلفة من 7 كيلو حتى 12 كيلو بأسعار تبدأ من 10,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو سعر ثلاجة توشيبا 16 قدم؟",
      "answer": "ثلاجة توشيبا 16 قدم نو فروست بسعر 14,500 جنيه بضمان 5 سنوات على الضاغط."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد أفران كهربائية؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا أفران كهربائية من تورنيدو، فريش، وبيكو بسعات مختلفة وأسعار تبدأ من 3,000 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هي أنواع السخانات المتوفرة؟",
      "answer": "لدينا سخانات فوري، تورنيدو، وايت بوينت كهرباء وغاز بسعات مختلفة وأسعار تبدأ من 2,500 جنيه."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد أجهزة تحضير طعام؟",
      "answer": "نعم، لدينا محضرات طعام من براون، كينوود، وفيليبس بأسعار تبدأ من 2,000 جنيه."
  },

  {
      "question": "هل تبيعون أجهزة آيباد مستعملة؟",
      "answer": "حاليًا لا نتعامل في الأجهزة المستعملة، جميع منتجاتنا جديدة وأصلية بضمان."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو هاتف الكاميرا الأفضل لديكم؟",
      "answer": "هاتف vivo X90 Pro بسعر 35,000 جنيه بكواد كاميرا 50 ميجابكسل مع عدسات ZEISS هو الأفضل للتصوير."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد هواتف ذاكرة 512GB؟",
      "answer": "نعم، iPhone 14 Pro وSamsung S23 Ultra متوفرين بإصدارات 512GB."
  },
  {
      "question": "ما هو أرخص لابتوب للطلاب؟",
      "answer": "لابتوب HP 15s بسعر 14,000 جنيه بمعالج Core i3 الجيل 11 مناسب للطلاب."
  },
  {
      "question": "هل يوجد عروض على التكييفات الصيفية؟",
      "answer": "نعم، حالياً خصم 15% على جميع التكييفات مع تركيب مجاني وهدية مراوح طاولة."
  },
 
    { question: 'What are the shipping dates?', answer: 'Shipping takes 1 to 3 business days within Cairo and Giza.' },
    { question: 'What are the working hours?', answer: 'We are available every day from 10 am to 8 pm, except Friday.' },
    { question: 'Can I return the product?', answer: 'Yes, you can return the product within 14 days from the date of receipt, provided that it is in its original condition.' },
    { question: 'What payment methods are available?', answer: 'We accept payment via credit card, PayPal, and cash on delivery.' },
    { question: 'Can I modify my order?', answer: 'You can modify your order before it is shipped, contact us through technical support.' },
    
  ,
        {
          "question": "Who are you?",
          "answer": "We are students from the Faculty of Science, Cairo University, Computer Science Department, and we are working on a project for course 303 with Dr. El-Gayar and Sameh."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where are you from?",
          "answer": "We are from Egypt."
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the team that developed the application?",
          "answer": "SuperMall team."
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the SuperMall application?",
          "answer": "SuperMall is an application where you'll find everything you need in terms of products, and you can say it's better than Amazon."
        },
        {
          "question": "What products does SuperMall offer?",
          "answer": "We offer a variety of products such as clothing and tech products."
        },
        {
          "question": "What distinguishes SuperMall from other websites?",
          "answer": "We are better and faster than other websites by a wide margin in terms of shipping and quality from our merchants."
        },
        {
          "question": "Are there promotions?",
          "answer": "Yes, there are promotions and discounts most of the year, and customers can browse products to follow offers."
        }
    
   ,
        {
          "question": "What is SuperMall?",
          "answer": "SuperMall is a modern e-commerce application that provides you with a seamless and fast shopping experience. Whether you're looking for the latest products, exclusive deals, or the best prices, we are here to meet your needs."
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the working hours at SuperMall?",
          "answer": "We work every day from 8 am to 12 midnight."
        },
        {
          "question": "Is there free shipping?",
          "answer": "Yes, and sometimes there might be free shipping."
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you ship to all governorates?",
          "answer": "Yes, shipping is done to all governorates."
        },
        {
          "question": "Is there cash on delivery?",
          "answer": "Yes, cash on delivery is available."
        },
        {
          "question": "How long does shipping take?",
          "answer": "Shipping times can reach up to 14 days maximum."
        },
        {
          "question": "On what system does the application work?",
          "answer": "The application system works on React Native."
        },
        {
          "question": "How can I contact the support team?",
          "answer": "You can contact the support team through the chatbot or via our Facebook page."
        },
        {
          "question": "Are there offers?",
          "answer": "Yes, there are offers and discounts most of the year, and customers can browse products to follow offers."
        },
  
        {
          "question": "What is SuperMall's mission?",
          "answer": "Our goal is to provide the best online shopping experience with high quality and excellent service, making shopping more enjoyable and accessible to everyone."
        },
        {
          "question": "Who are the members of the SuperMall team?",
          "answer": "The SuperMall team consists of a group of creative students from the Faculty of Science, Cairo University. Team members are: Ahmed Ezz Eldin Khalili, Abdelrahman Ahmed Helmy, Bavly Momtaz, Ramadan Abdel Nasser, Ahmed Saeed, Anas Jamal, Abdelrahman Ihab, Abdullah Ali Khamis."
        },
        {
          "question": "What does SuperMall offer to users?",
          "answer": "SuperMall offers a unique shopping experience with various high-quality products, exclusive offers, and fast shipping."
        },
        {
          "question": "Is there free shipping at SuperMall?",
          "answer": "Yes, we have free shipping times for customers."
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the working hours at SuperMall?",
          "answer": "We work daily from 8 am until 12 midnight."
        },
        {
          "question": "Where does the SuperMall team come from?",
          "answer": "The SuperMall team is a group of students from Egypt, from the Faculty of Science, Cairo University, Computer Science Department."
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you ship to all governorates?",
          "answer": "Yes, we provide shipping service to all governorates in Egypt."
        },
        {
          "question": "Who developed the chatbot?",
          "answer": "The chatbot was developed by Helmy."
        },
        {
          "question": "What is SuperMall?",
          "answer": "SuperMall is an application where you'll find all the products you need and might be better than Amazon."
        },
        {
          "question": "Does the SuperMall app work on the React Native platform?",
          "answer": "Yes, the SuperMall app works on React Native, providing you with an excellent and smooth user experience on all devices."
        },
        {
          "question": "Can I follow offers on SuperMall?",
          "answer": "Yes, you can easily browse all products through the app or website."
        },
        {
          "question": "Is free shipping available at SuperMall?",
          "answer": "Yes, at certain times, we offer free shipping for all our customers."
        }
   ,
   {
    "question": "What are the working hours at SuperMall?",
    "answer": "We work every day of the week from 8 am to 12 midnight."
  }
  ,
  {
    "question": "Is there free shipping?",
    "answer": "Yes, and sometimes there might be free shipping."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you ship to all governorates?",
    "answer": "Yes, shipping is done to all governorates."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there cash on delivery?",
    "answer": "Yes, cash on delivery is available."
  },
  {
    "question": "How long does shipping take?",
    "answer": "Shipping times can reach up to 14 days maximum."
  },
  {
    "question": "On what system does the app work?",
    "answer": "The application system works on React Native."
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I contact the support team?",
    "answer": "You can contact the support team through the chatbot or via our Facebook page."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there offers?",
    "answer": "Yes, there are offers and discounts most of the year, and customers can browse products to follow offers."
  },
  
  {
    "question": "Can I buy food from SuperMall?",
    "answer": "Currently, we do not offer food purchase services, but there are plans to add food products in the future."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is multilingual support available in the app?",
    "answer": "Currently the app only supports Arabic."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I track the status of my order?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can track your order status through the app or through the shipping link sent to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do special offers exist for new customers at SuperMall?",
    "answer": "Yes, we offer special discounts for new customers when registering in the app for the first time."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I buy gifts from SuperMall?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can buy gifts from various departments such as clothing and electronics."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are prices regularly updated at SuperMall?",
    "answer": "Yes, prices are updated periodically to match the market."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the return conditions in SuperMall?",
    "answer": "The product must be in its original condition with the invoice present within 14 days of receipt."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I cancel my order after payment?",
    "answer": "You can cancel the order before it is shipped, and contact the support team to complete the cancellation."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have a 24/7 customer service?",
    "answer": "We are available from 8 am to 12 pm daily except Friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a gift wrapping service?",
    "answer": "Currently, we do not offer gift wrapping service."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I buy home appliances from SuperMall?",
    "answer": "Yes, we have a special section for home appliances such as washing machines, microwaves, and others."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are new products added regularly?",
    "answer": "Yes, we add new products periodically in various categories."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I purchase products from famous brands?",
    "answer": "Yes, we have products from famous brands in different categories."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I contact customer support by phone?",
    "answer": "Currently, support is only available via chatbot or our Facebook page."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you send me a link to the product?",
    "answer": "Yes, we can send you a product link through the app or via email."
  },
  
  {
    "question": "What payment methods are available at SuperMall?",
    "answer": "We accept payment via credit card, PayPal, and cash on delivery."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I change the shipping address after submitting the order?",
    "answer": "Yes, the address can be changed provided that the order has not been shipped yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I purchase new products through the website?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can easily purchase new products through the website or app."
  },
  {
    "question": "Are there any discounts for large orders?",
    "answer": "Yes, we offer discounts of up to 20% for orders over 1000 pounds."
  },
  {
      "question": "How can I create an account on SuperMall?",
      "answer": "You can easily create an account via email or phone number through the app or website."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I save products in a favorites list?",
      "answer": "Yes, you can add any product to favorites by clicking on the heart icon next to the product."
  },
  {
      "question": "What is SuperMall's privacy policy?",
      "answer": "We respect our customers' privacy and do not share your personal data with any external parties."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I buy pet products?",
      "answer": "Currently we do not offer pet products but they may be added in the future."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a books section in SuperMall?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a section for books of all kinds including educational books and novels."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I buy sports products?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a special section for sports products and sports equipment."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a SuperMall app for Android?",
      "answer": "Yes, you can download our official app from the Google Play store."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a SuperMall app for iPhone?",
      "answer": "Yes, the app is available on the Apple store for download."
  },
  {
      "question": "How can I reset my password?",
      "answer": "You can use the 'Forgot Password' feature on the login page."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I change the app language?",
      "answer": "Currently the app only supports Arabic."
  },
  {
      "question": "What are the terms of use for SuperMall?",
      "answer": "You can view the full terms of use in the 'Terms and Conditions' section of the website."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I share products with friends?",
      "answer": "Yes, there is a share button next to each product to share it via social media."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a product rating system?",
      "answer": "Yes, you can rate products you have purchased through your account."
  },
  {
      "question": "How can I know about the available clothing sizes?",
      "answer": "All available sizes appear on the product page under the 'Sizes' section."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I order a product that is currently not available?",
      "answer": "Yes, you can contact customer service to order a product that is not available."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a section for children at SuperMall?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a special section for children's clothing and toys."
  },
  {
      "question": "Can I buy beauty products?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a special section for beauty products and personal care."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is there a perfume section?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a variety of local and international perfumes."
  },
  
  {
      "question": "When do discount offers start at SuperMall?",
      "answer": "Discount offers usually start on occasions and holidays and we announce them in advance."
  },
  {
      "question": "Are there special offers on holidays?",
      "answer": "Yes, we offer special offers for all holidays and occasions."
  },
  {
      "question": "How do I know if a product is discounted?",
      "answer": "Discounted products have a discount mark and show the price before and after the discount."
  },
  
  {
      "question": "How can I ensure the quality of products?",
      "answer": "All our products are from reliable suppliers and you can read customer reviews."
  },
  {
      "question": "Do you provide a warranty on electronic devices?",
      "answer": "Yes, electronic devices come with an official factory warranty."
  },
  
  {
      "question": "How can I become a partner in SuperMall?",
      "answer": "You can contact the partnerships department through the official website."
  },
  {
      "question": "Do you have an affiliate marketing program?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have an affiliate marketing program you can join."
  },
  
  {
      "question": "What are the system requirements for running the app?",
      "answer": "The app works on Android 8 or higher, and iPhone iOS 12 or newer."
  },
  {
      "question": "Is the app safe to use?",
      "answer": "Yes, the app is completely safe and uses encryption to protect your data."
  },
  
  {
      "question": "Can I choose the delivery time?",
      "answer": "Yes, in some areas you can specify the delivery time that suits you."
  },
  {
      "question": "What shipping companies do you deal with?",
      "answer": "We deal with several reliable shipping companies to ensure your order arrives safely."
  },
  
  
  {
      "question": "Do you sell home furniture?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a section for home furniture of various types."
  },
  {
      "question": "Are there cooking utensils in SuperMall?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a variety of cooking utensils and kitchen items."
  },
  
  
  {
      "question": "Do you sell air conditioners?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a selection of air conditioners from international brands."
  },
  {
      "question": "Are there dishwashers?",
      "answer": "Yes, we have a complete section for home appliances including dishwashers."
  },
  
  
    {
        "question": "What are the latest iPhone phones available?",
        "answer": "We have the latest iPhone models including iPhone 15 Pro Max for 45,000 pounds, iPhone 15 Pro for 40,000 pounds, and iPhone 15 for 35,000 pounds. All come with Super Retina XDR displays and A16 Bionic processors."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there Samsung Galaxy S23 phones?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have the Samsung Galaxy S23 Ultra for 38,000 pounds with a 6.8-inch Dynamic AMOLED 2X display, 200-megapixel camera, and Galaxy S23+ for 32,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cheapest smartphone you have?",
        "answer": "Realme C35 phone for 5,999 pounds with a 6.6-inch screen, triple 50-megapixel camera, and 5000 mAh battery."
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you sell Xiaomi phones?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have Xiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro for 12,999 pounds, and Xiaomi 13T Pro for 24,999 pounds with high-quality specifications."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best gaming phone you have?",
        "answer": "ASUS ROG Phone 7 for 30,000 pounds with Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 processor, 165Hz AMOLED screen, and efficient cooling for heavy games."
    },
  
    {
        "question": "What laptop devices do you have?",
        "answer": "We have a diverse range of laptops including: Dell Inspiron 15 for 18,000 pounds, HP Pavilion for 22,000 pounds, Lenovo IdeaPad Gaming 3 for 25,000 pounds, and MacBook Air M2 for 35,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there gaming laptops?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have laptops dedicated to gaming such as: MSI Katana GF76 for 40,000 pounds, ASUS TUF Gaming F15 for 38,000 pounds, and Acer Nitro 5 for 35,000 pounds with high gaming specifications."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cheapest laptop you have?",
        "answer": "Lenovo IdeaPad 1 laptop for 12,000 pounds with a 14-inch screen, Intel Celeron processor, and 4GB RAM, suitable for basic tasks."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there MacBook devices?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have MacBook Air M1 for 30,000 pounds, MacBook Air M2 for 35,000 pounds, and MacBook Pro 14-inch M2 Pro for 65,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best laptop for programming?",
        "answer": "We recommend Dell XPS 15 for 55,000 pounds with Core i7 processor, 16GB RAM, and 512GB SSD, or MacBook Pro 14-inch for developers working on Apple systems."
    },
  
    {
        "question": "What tablets do you have?",
        "answer": "We have: iPad 10th Gen for 18,000 pounds, Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 for 25,000 pounds, Huawei MatePad for 12,000 pounds, and Lenovo Tab P11 for 9,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there an iPad Pro?",
        "answer": "Yes, iPad Pro 11-inch M2 for 32,000 pounds, and iPad Pro 12.9-inch M2 for 45,000 pounds with Liquid Retina XDR display."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best tablet for digital drawing?",
        "answer": "iPad Pro with Apple Pencil is the best choice for digital drawing, or Samsung Galaxy Tab S9 with S-Pen which comes with an AMOLED screen."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there tablets for children?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have Lenovo Tab M10 Kids Edition for 6,000 pounds with shock protection and built-in educational content."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cheapest tablet you have?",
        "answer": "Samsung Galaxy Tab A7 Lite tablet for 4,500 pounds with an 8.7-inch screen, suitable for basic tasks and watching videos."
    },
  
    {
        "question": "What types of air conditioners do you have?",
        "answer": "We have air conditioners from Sharp, Tornado, Carrier, and Gree in all their types (split, window, stand) and with different capacities starting from 1.5 HP up to 3 HP."
    },
    {
        "question": "How much does a 1.5 HP Sharp air conditioner cost?",
        "answer": "Sharp split 1.5 HP hot and cold air conditioner for 18,000 pounds with a 5-year warranty on the compressor."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there inverter air conditioners?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have Gree Inverter 1.5 HP A++ air conditioner for 22,000 pounds that saves up to 60% of electricity consumption."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best air conditioner in terms of power saving?",
        "answer": "Tornado Inverter 1.5 HP A+++ air conditioner is the best in saving for 24,000 pounds with smart power control technology."
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you provide air conditioner installation service?",
        "answer": "Yes, we offer free installation service with any air conditioner you purchase from us with a one-year installation warranty."
    },
  
    {
        "question": "Are there automatic washing machines?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have washing machines from Toshiba, Samsung, and LG with different capacities from 7 kg to 12 kg starting from 10,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is a 16-foot Toshiba refrigerator?",
        "answer": "16-foot Toshiba No Frost refrigerator for 14,500 pounds with a 5-year warranty on the compressor."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there electric ovens?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have electric ovens from Tornado, Fresh, and Beko with different capacities and prices starting from 3,000 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "What types of heaters are available?",
        "answer": "We have instant, Tornado, and White Point heaters for electricity and gas with different capacities and prices starting from 2,500 pounds."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there food preparation devices?",
        "answer": "Yes, we have food processors from Braun, Kenwood, and Philips with prices starting from 2,000 pounds."
    },
  
    {
        "question": "Do you sell used iPad devices?",
        "answer": "Currently we do not deal in used devices, all our products are new and original with warranty."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the best camera phone you have?",
        "answer": "vivo X90 Pro phone for 35,000 pounds with a quad 50-megapixel camera with ZEISS lenses is the best for photography."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there 512GB memory phones?",
        "answer": "Yes, iPhone 14 Pro and Samsung S23 Ultra are available in 512GB versions."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cheapest laptop for students?",
        "answer": "HP 15s laptop for 14,000 pounds with 11th Gen Core i3 processor suitable for students."
    },
    {
        "question": "Are there offers on summer air conditioners?",
        "answer": "Yes, currently 15% off on all air conditioners with free installation and a table fan gift."
    },
  ];
  
  
